Alexander Petrunkevitch Archives
Yale Peabody Museum of Natural History
- Correspondence, Series I
  - Schultze, Jena. EST number of items = 1., 1932; 002248
  - Schwarz, H.F. EST number of items = 1., 1931; 002247
  - Scientific American. EST number of items= 15+., 1950-1958; 001897
  - Scott, H.W. EST number of items = 2., 1949; 002243
  - Scully, Dorothy W. EST number of items = 1., 1949; 002244
  - Sekiguchi, K. EST number of items = 1., 1949; 002249
  - Semans, Frank M. EST number of items = 1., 1937; 002250
  - Sembrat, K. EST number of items = 3., 1949; 002251
  - Setterlind, A.N. EST number of items = 2., 1945; 002252
  - Sexauer, H.F. EST number of items = 1., 002253
  - Seydel, CH. EST number of items= 1., 1946; 002353
  - Sherriffs, W.R. EST number of items = 10+., 1926-1951; 002245
  - Shoemaker, C.R. EST number of items = 5+., 1924-1930; 002254
  - Shrock, R.R. EST number of items = 5+., 1949-1951; 002255
  - Shuster, Carl N. EST number of items = 2., 1950-1951; 002256
  - Silvestri, F. EST number of items = 3., 1930-1947; 002257
  - Simpson, G.G. EST number of items = 3., 1945-1949; 002258
  - Sinha, T.B. EST number of items = 1., 1950; 002259
  - Smith, B.L. EST number of items = 1., 1952; 002262
  - Smith, L.M. EST number of items = 3., 1945; 002263
  - Smithers, R.H. EST number of items = 10+. Pictures included., 1937-1949; 002264
  - Smyth, L.B. EST number of items = 2., 1948; 002265
  - Snell, F.M. EST number of items = 2., 1924; 002266
  - Snodgrass, R.E. EST number of items = 2., 1922-1949; 002267
  - Society of Systematic Zoologists. EST number of items = 50+. Correspondence notably between Schmitt, W.L., Wharton G.W., Blackwelder R.E., Pennak, R.W., Gunter G., Pennak, R.W. All members of the Society of Systematic Zoologists., 1947-1954; 002326
  - Sornay, J. EST number of items = 2., 1959; 002269
  - Souto, A. EST number of items = 2., 1945; 002268
  - Spassky, S.A. EST number of items = 5., 1927-1931; 002270
  - Spencer, C.S. EST number of items = 5+., 1929; 002271
  - Steinitz, H. EST number of items = 2., 1953-1954; 002272
  - Stensio, Erik. EST number of items = 2., 1949-1950; 002273
  - Stern, Curt. EST number of items = 2., 1945; 002274
  - Stiles, C.W. EST number of items = 5+., 1928; 002275
  - Stokes, A.P. EST number of items = 3., 1918-1921; 002277
  - Stomer, L. EST number of items = 5+., 1932-1951; 002278
  - Stone, L. EST number of items = 1., 1956; 002279
  - Strand, E. EST number of items = 5+., 1923-1942; 002276
  - Straw, S.H. EST number of items = 1., 1950; 002280
  - Stubblefield, C.J. EST number of items = 3., 1949-1953; 002281
  - Stultz, Harold T. EST number of items = 1., 1945; 002282
  - Stumm, Erwin C. EST number of items = 1., 1957; 002283
  - Suzuki, S. EST number of items = 1., 1951; 002284
  - Swartz, Frank M. EST number of items = 1., 1950; 002285
  - Swift, H.H. EST number of items = 1., 1947; 002286
  - Tanquy, C.R. EST number of items = 2., 1958; 002287
  - Tee-Van, John. EST number of items = 1., 1949; 002288
  - Teixeira,C. EST number of items = 1., 1953; 002354
  - Teuscher, W.P. EST number of items = 1., 1950; 002289
  - Theuer, Bert. EST number of items = 2., 1941-1951; 002290
  - Thomas, M. EST number of items = 5+., 1926-1929; 002291
  - Thompson, H.K. EST number of items = 1., 1965; 002292
  - Tillson, A. EST number of items = 1., 1947; 002293
  - Tirelli, Mario. EST number of items = 1., 1948; 002294
  - Titus, C.P. EST number of items = 1., 1922; 002295
  - Tobar, R.G. EST number of items = 5+., 1946-1953; 002296
  - Todd, Valerie. EST number of items = 1., 1947; 002297
  - Torrey, Charles. EST number of items = 2., 1954; 002298
  - Trossarelli, F. EST number of items = 5+., 1929-1949; 002299
  - Trueman, A. EST number of items = 1., 1950; 002300
  - Turk, F.A. EST number of items = 3., 1952; 002301
  - Tyler, Ruth. EST number of items = 1., 1946; 002302
  - University of California. EST number of items = 20+. Most from Paul D. Hurd., 1958-1964; 002303
  - University of Porto Rico. EST number of items = 15+., 1925-1964; 002304
  - Unknown. EST number of items = 20+. Various Correspondence to & from A. Petrunkevitch that is either un labled or unlegible., 002369
  - Uriel, M. EST number of items = 1., 1944; 002305
  - Vachon, Max. EST number of items = 3., 1952-1953; 002306
  - Valentine, Manson. EST number of items = 5+., 1929-1962; 002307
  - Van Riper, Walker. EST number of items = 5+., 1944; 002308
  - Vellard, J. EST number of items = 2., 1949-1952; 002309
  - Vishniac, R. EST number of items = 1., 1951; 002310
  - Vosburg, J.F. EST number of items = 2., 1950; 002311
  - Walker, Roland. EST number of items = 1., 1946; 002312
  - Walker, Williston. EST number of items = 5., 1921; 002313
  - Wallace, H.K. EST number of items = 5+., 1938-1950; 002314
  - Wang, K.S. EST number of items = 1., 1921; 002315
  - Wang, Y.M. EST number of items = 1., 1952; 002316
  - Ward, Henry B. EST number of items = 1., 1933; 002317
  - Warne, C.E. EST number of items = 1., 1950; 002318
  - Welch, Paul S. EST number of items = 3., 1947; 002319
  - Weller, M. J. EST number of items = 1., 1949; 002320
  - Welsh, J.H. EST number of items = 1., 1947; 002321
  - West, A.S. EST number of items = 1., 1951; 002322
  - Westergard, A.H. EST number of items = 3., 1949-1952; 002323
  - Westoll, T.S. EST number of items = 5+., 1949; 002324
  - Wetmore, A. EST number of items = 5+., 1927-1947; 002325
  - Wheeler, W.M. EST number of items = 2., 1926; 002327
  - Whittington, H.B. EST number of items = 2., 1949-1960; 002328
  - Wiehle, H. EST number of items = 5+., 1929-1931; 002329
  - Williams, C.E. EST number of items = 2., 1945; 002330
  - Willier, B.H. EST number of items = 2., 1950; 002331
  - Wills, L.J. EST number of items = 5+., 1949-1950; 002332
  - Wilson, Edwin B. EST number of items = 5+., 1924-1937; 002333
  - Wilson, H.V. EST number of items = 1., 002334
  - Wilson, Leonard G. EST number of items = 2., 1962; 002335
  - Wilson, Thomas J. EST number of items = 1., 1956; 002336
  - Wing, M.W. EST number of items = 2., 1947; 002337
  - Witherspoon, A.M. EST number of items = 1., 1963; 002338
  - Wolcott, R.H. EST number of items = 3., 1921; 002339
  - Wood, A.E. EST number of items = 1., 1949; 002340
  - Wood, H.E. EST number of items = 5+., 1945-1951; 002341
  - Wood, J.M. EST number of items = 5+., 1955; 002342
  - Woods, Henry. EST number of items = 1., 1934; 002368
  - Woodson, Welden D. EST number of items = 3., 1945-1951; 002343
  - Wozniak, R. J. EST number of items = 2., 1944; 002344
  - Wrather, W.E. EST number of items = 2., 1951; 002345
  - Wright, Gilbert. EST number of items = 5+., 1842-1943; 002346
  - Wylie, Fred H. EST number of items = 5+., 1943-1944; 002347
  - Yabe, H. EST number of items = 2., 1949-1952; 002348
  - Yale Literary Magazine. EST number of items = 2., 002349
  - Zetek, James. EST number of items = 2., 1938; 002350
  - Zimmerman, E. C. EST number of items = 2., 1952-1954; 002351
  - Zoological Society of London. EST number of items = 1., 1948; 002352
- Manuscript Materials, Series II
  Scope and Contents
  Original Manuscripts, materials and supporting documants from Alexander Petrunkevitch.
  - Data & Supporting Documents. Data and documents supporting Alexander Petrunkevitch's manuscripts. 3 boxes., 002095
  - Original Manuscripts. Collection of Alexander Petrunkevitch's original manuscripts. 4 boxes., 002094
- Biographical Materials, Series III
  Biographical material for Alexaner Petrunkevitch.
  - Biographical Information. Various biographical paper work including Death certification, life timeline, Obituaries etc., 002376
  - Biographical Memoirs. Memours written by Charles Timberlake and G.E. Hutchinson., 002375
  - Census. Copy of the cencus filled out by A. Petrunkevitch., 1930; 002371
  - Curriculm Vitae., 002372
  - Honors. Honors and awards recieved bu A. Petrunkevitch., 002373
  - Retirement. Various resources used for planing the suprise party and manuscript in the honor of Alexander Petrunkevitch's retirement., 002374
- Yale Teaching Materials, Series IV
  Materials used for leactures and labs during A. Petrunkevitch's time as a professor of Zoology at Yale University.
  - Arachnida Keys. EST number of items= 10+., 002378
  - Histology., 002379
  - Lectures & Essays. Class and public lectures as well as essays by Alexander Petrunkevitch., 002386
  - Memorandums., 002380
- Affiliations, Series V
  Clubs and societies that Alexander Petrunkevitch belonged to.
  - C.I.D.A. Centre International De Documentation Arachnoloqique. EST number of items = 5+., 002385
  - Pacific Science Association. Pacicic Science Association standing committee on Pacific Entomology. Pictures included., 1958-1963; 002383
  - Society of Systematic Zoology., 1947-1949; 002382
  - The Club., 1914-1949; 002384
- Field Work, Series VI
  Materials used in the feild by A. Petrunkevitch such ad maps and field books.
  - Maps. Various maps from all over the world used by Alexander Petrunkevitch., 002389
  - Notebooks. Field notes and notebooks used by Alexander Petrunkevitch. Undated., 002388
- Photographs, Series VII
  - Miscellaneous., 002719